[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_B",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_01_Periville_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_title",
        "Description": "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_01_Periville_completion",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_C",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_title",
        "Description": "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_02_Karburg_completion",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_D",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_title",
        "Description": "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_03_AncientBridge_completion",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_BellaRuby",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_title",
        "Description": "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_04_Settlement01_completion",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_E",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_title",
        "Description": "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_05_FindMorgaine_completion",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Galahad_E",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_title",
        "Description": "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_06_WitchMagic_completion",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_B",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_title",
        "Description": "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_07_DestroyBarrier_completion",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_C",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_title",
        "Description": "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_08_Settlement02_completion",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_D",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_title",
        "Description": "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_09_Canopus_completion",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_D",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_title",
        "Description": "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_10_Andrometus_completion",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99C_Morgaine_D",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "CoatingAeternianT4",
        "ItemRewardQty": 3,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_title",
        "Description": "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_11_Lepus_completion",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "NPC_9902_MSQ_Yonas",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99C_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99C_MSQ_12_Vector_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_title",
        "Description": "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99C_MSQ_12_Vector_completion",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
